<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="quote_1">“People who love to eat are always the best people.”</string>
    <string name="quote_2">“One cannot think well, love well, sleep well if one has not dined well.”</string>
    <string name="quote_3">“Life is uncertain. Eat dessert first.”</string>
    <string name="quote_4">“Cooking is like love. It should be entered into with abandon or not at all”</string>
    <string name="quote_5">“We all eat, and it would be a sad waste of opportunity to eat badly.”</string>
    <string name="quote_6">“You don’t need a silver fork to eat good food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_7">“There is no sincere love than the love of food..”</string>
    <string name="quote_8">“Pull up a chair.Take a taste.Come join us.Life is so endlessly delicious.”</string>
    <string name="quote_9">“A recipe has no soul. You, as the cook, must bring soul to the recipe.”</string>
    <string name="quote_10">“Good food is the foundation of genuine happiness.”</string>
    <string name="quote_11">“The only thing I like better than talking about food is eating.”</string>
    <string name="quote_12">“Food is symbolic of love when words are inadequate.”</string>
    <string name="quote_13">“You are what you eat, so don’t be fast, cheap, easy, or fake.”</string>
    <string name="quote_14">“The secret of success in life is to eat what you like and let the food fight it out inside.”</string>
    <string name="quote_15">“Laughter is brightest in the place where food is.”</string>
    <string name="quote_16">“Happiness is homemade.”</string>
    <string name="quote_17">“Food brings people together on many different levels. It’s nourishment of the soul and body; it’s truly love.”</string>
    <string name="quote_18">“I cook with wine, sometimes I even add it to the food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_19">“First, we eat. Then, we do everything else.”</string>
    <string name="quote_20">“Cooking and eating is as timeless as a heartbeat.”</string>
    <string name="quote_21">“There’s no better feeling in the world than a warm pizza box on your lap.”</string>
    <string name="quote_22">“In wine, there is wisdom. In beer, there is freedom. In water, there is bacteria.”</string>
    <string name="quote_23">“You don’t have to cook fancy or complicated masterpieces – just good food from fresh ingredients.”</string>
    <string name="quote_24">“Eat breakfast like a king, lunch like a prince, and dinner like a pauper.”</string>
    <string name="quote_25">“I am not a glutton. I am an explorer of food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_26">“Food is the ingredient that binds us together.”</string>
    <string name="quote_27">“A balanced diet is a cookie in each hand.”</string>
    <string name="quote_28">“Food is not rational. Food is culture, habit, craving, and identity.”</string>
    <string name="quote_29">“The belly rules the mind.”</string>
    <string name="quote_30">“Count the memories, not the calories.”</string>
    <string name="quote_31">“Good food is all the sweeter when shared with good friends.”</string>
    <string name="quote_32">“Love and sausage are alike. Can never have enough of either.”</string>
    <string name="quote_33">“There’s nothing more romantic than Italian food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_34">“All happiness depends on a leisurely breakfast.”</string>
    <string name="quote_35">“Food is fuel, but good food is soul fuel.”</string>
    <string name="quote_36">“There is no love sincerer than the love of food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_37">“Let food be thy medicine and medicine be thy food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_38">“Nothing brings people together like good food.”</string>
    <string name="quote_39">“My weaknesses have always been food and men – in that order.”</string>
    <string name="quote_40">“Eating is a necessity, but cooking is an art”</string>


</resources>